<?xml version='1.0' ?><rss version='2.0'><Campings><item><id>7</id><name>Motorhome Park</name><content>Welcome to Motorhome Park, a camping haven for adventurers and nature enthusiasts. Nestled amid the heart of the great outdoors, Motorhome Park offers a unique camping experience that combines the comforts of home with the beauty of nature. Set up camp with your trusty motorhome in a spacious and well-equipped park that provides modern facilities and easy access to the region&#039;s stunning attractions. Whether you&#039;re an experienced camper or new to the world of outdoor living, Motorhome Park ensures that your camping adventure is both enjoyable and hassle-free. So, get ready to park your motorhome in a serene natural setting, unwind by the campfire, and create lasting memories in the great outdoors.</content><capacity>62.00</capacity><priceperday>camp</priceperday><image>Motorhome Park</image></item><item><id>8</id><name>Cabin Wood</name><content>Welcome to Cabin Wood, where rustic charm meets modern comfort in the heart of the wilderness. Our cozy cabins are nestled among towering trees and provide the perfect escape for those seeking an authentic camping experience. Each cabin is equipped with all the amenities you need for a comfortable stay, while the surrounding woods offer endless opportunities for outdoor adventures. Whether you&#039;re looking to hike, fish, or simply unwind by the campfire, Cabin Wood has it all. Experience the serenity of the woods, immerse yourself in the natural beauty, and create unforgettable memories with family and friends.</content><capacity>47.90</capacity><priceperday>camp</priceperday><image>Cabin Wood</image></item><item><id>9</id><name>Tent Park</name><content>At Tent Park, we invite you to embark on an unforgettable camping journey under the open skies. Pitch your tent in our spacious, well-maintained campgrounds and connect with nature in its purest form. Enjoy the simplicity of a night under the stars, the crackling of a campfire, and the soothing sounds of the great outdoors. Our campgrounds offer various amenities to make your stay comfortable, ensuring a relaxing experience while you commune with nature. Whether you&#039;re a seasoned camper or trying it for the first time, Tent Park is your gateway to adventure, serenity, and the ultimate camping experience.</content><capacity>31.00</capacity><priceperday>camp</priceperday><image>Tent Park</image></item><item><id>10</id><name>River View Tent</name><content>Experience the thrill of camping by the riverside at River View Tent. Nestled along the banks of a pristine river, our campground offers a unique and tranquil setting for your camping escapade. You&#039;ll awaken to the soothing sounds of flowing water and enjoy the peaceful ambiance of the surrounding forest. Our spacious and comfortable tents are strategically placed to provide breathtaking views of the river, allowing you to connect with nature in a way that&#039;s truly extraordinary. Enjoy leisurely walks along the riverbank, indulge in water activities, and savor the beauty of the natural world. River View Tent is your exclusive pass to an enchanting outdoor retreat where adventure and relaxation meet harmoniously.</content><capacity>35.50</capacity><priceperday>camp</priceperday><image>River View Tent</image></item><item><id>11</id><name>Caravan</name><content>Welcome to Caravan, where the road becomes your home and adventure is just a drive away. Our campsite is specially designed for those who prefer the convenience and mobility of caravanning. Whether you&#039;re a seasoned traveler or a first-time adventurer, Caravan offers a safe and comfortable space for you to park your home-on-wheels. Set amidst picturesque landscapes, our well-equipped facilities ensure you have everything you need, from water and electricity hook-ups to modern amenities. Enjoy the freedom to explore, as Caravan provides an excellent base for your journey into the great outdoors. Discover the magic of open roads, scenic vistas, and endless possibilities as you embark on your caravan adventure at Caravan Campsite.</content><capacity>52.20</capacity><priceperday>camp</priceperday><image>Caravan</image></item><item><id>12</id><name>Safari Tent</name><content>Experience the thrill of the wild in comfort and style at Safari Tent Camp. Nestled in the heart of nature, our luxury safari tents offer a unique camping experience. These spacious and beautifully furnished tents provide a cozy retreat for adventurers seeking a touch of elegance while being close to the great outdoors. Imagine waking up to the sounds of the wilderness, enjoying the warm embrace of a comfortable bed, and stepping onto your private deck to witness the beauty of untouched landscapes. At Safari Tent Camp, we combine the best of both worlds, allowing you to connect with nature without sacrificing modern comfort. Embark on an unforgettable safari experience at Safari Tent Camp, where adventure and luxury meet under the open skies.</content><capacity>42.20</capacity><priceperday>camp</priceperday><image>Safari Tent</image></item></Campings></rss>