<?xml version='1.0' ?><rss version='2.0'><Swimmings><item><id>1</id><name>Crystal Oasis</name><content>Discover a true gem among swimming destinations at the Crystal Oasis. The waters here are known for their remarkable clarity, allowing you to see the mosaic of underwater treasures beneath you. It&#039;s a place where you can experience both serenity and the enchantment of nature&#039;s aquatic wonders as you take a dip in these pristine waters.</content><capacity>52.50</capacity><priceperday>swim</priceperday><image>Crystal Oasis</image></item><item><id>2</id><name>Nature Lagoon</name><content>Immerse yourself in the untouched beauty of the Nature Lagoon. Surrounded by lush greenery and teeming with indigenous flora and fauna, this lagoon offers a unique and refreshing wild swimming experience. The tranquil waters are perfect for a leisurely dip, allowing you to connect with the natural world in an unforgettable way. Come and unwind in the serenity of the Nature Lagoon and escape into the heart of the wilderness.</content><capacity>46.80</capacity><priceperday>swim</priceperday><image>Nature Lagoon</image></item><item><id>3</id><name>Starlight Lake</name><content>Dive into the shimmering waters of Starlight Lake and discover a hidden gem under the open sky. As the day fades, the lake comes alive with the glimmer of countless stars, creating a breathtaking celestial display reflected on the water&#039;s surface. It&#039;s the ideal spot for an evening swim, making you feel like you&#039;re bathing in the cosmos. Starlight Lake promises an otherworldly experience, combining the beauty of nature with the wonders of the night sky for an unforgettable adventure.</content><capacity>33.06</capacity><priceperday>swim</priceperday><image>Starlight Lake</image></item><item><id>4</id><name>Wildness River</name><content>Prepare to be swept away by the untamed beauty of Wildness River. This pristine waterway takes you on a journey through lush forests and rugged terrain, offering the ultimate wild swimming adventure. Immerse yourself in crystal-clear waters and let the current carry you through picturesque landscapes. The river is a sanctuary for both nature enthusiasts and thrill-seekers, where you can cool off while exploring the unspoiled wilderness. With its diverse flora and fauna, Wildness River is an idyllic destination for those seeking an authentic and immersive outdoor experience.</content><capacity>37.40</capacity><priceperday>swim</priceperday><image>Wildness River</image></item><item><id>5</id><name>Rocky Fall</name><content>If you&#039;re in search of a unique swimming spot that combines natural beauty with a dash of adventure, Rocky Fall is the perfect destination. Nestled within a rocky canyon, this scenic location boasts stunning waterfalls and emerald-green pools that are ideal for swimming. The landscape is characterized by its rugged, rocky terrain, providing both an adrenaline rush and a tranquil escape from the everyday. As you take a plunge into the refreshing waters and swim beneath the cascading falls, you&#039;ll be surrounded by the soothing sounds of nature. Rocky Fall offers an extraordinary experience for swimmers who appreciate the harmony of serenity and excitement.</content><capacity>26.50</capacity><priceperday>swim</priceperday><image>Rocky Fall</image></item><item><id>6</id><name>Riverside Oasis</name><content>Unveil the enchanting beauty of Riverside Oasis, a serene and picturesque swimming location that invites you to indulge in relaxation and recreation. Situated alongside a meandering river, this hidden gem offers a cool respite from the heat and a tranquil escape from the bustle of everyday life. With its lush greenery, gentle currents, and crystal-clear waters, Riverside Oasis is the ideal place for a leisurely swim. Immerse yourself in the refreshing river, unwind on the peaceful riverbanks, or explore the adjacent nature trails. Whether you&#039;re looking for a peaceful sun-soaked day or a leisurely swim under the open sky, Riverside Oasis promises an idyllic setting for nature lovers and water enthusiasts alike.</content><capacity>18.20</capacity><priceperday>swim</priceperday><image>Riverside Oasis</image></item></Swimmings></rss>